<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.labplot2.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Labplot</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxLabPlotxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">LabPlot</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">LabPlot</name>
  <summary>Interactive graphing and analysis of scientific data</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Representació interactiva de grafs i anàlisi de dades científiques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Representació interactiva de grafs i anàlisi de dades científiques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Interaktivní vykreslování grafů a analýza vědeckých dat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Interaktiven Erstellung von Grafiken und Analyse wissenschaftlicher Daten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Interactive graphing and analysis of scientific data</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gráficos interactivos y análisis de datos científicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Teaduslike andmete interaktiivse graafikuna esitamine ja analüüs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Datu zientifikoak modu elkarreragilean grafikatu eta aztertu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Tracé interactif de courbes et analyse de données scientifiques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xeración interactiva de gráficos e a análise de datos científicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Penggrafikan yang interaktif dan analisis data ilmiah</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Grafici interattivi e analisi dei dati scientifici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Interactief maken van grafieken en analyseren van wetenschappelijke gegevens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Interaktiv plotting og analyse av vitskaplege data</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Interaktywne przestawianie graficzne i analizy danych naukowych</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gráficos interactivos e análise de dados científicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de gráficos interativos e análise de dados científicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">LabPlot — анализ экспериментальных данных с возможностью интерактивного построения графиков</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Interaktívne grafy a analýza vedeckých údajov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Interaktivni grafični prikaz in analiza znanstvenih podatkov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Interaktiv diagramritning och analys av vetenskaplig data</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтерактивна побудова графіків та аналіз наукових даних</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxInteractive graphing and analysis of scientific dataxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      LabPlot is an application for interactive graphing and analysis of scientific data.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El LabPlot és una aplicació per a la representació interactiva de grafs i anàlisi de dades científiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El LabPlot és una aplicació per a la representació interactiva de grafs i anàlisi de dades científiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">LabPlot je aplikace pro interaktivní vykreslování grafů a analýzu vědeckých dat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">LabPlot ist eine Anwendung zur interaktiven Erstellung von Grafiken und Analyse wissenschaftlicher Daten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">LabPlot is an application for interactive graphing and analysis of scientific data.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">LabPlot es una aplicación para gráficos interactivos y análisis de datos científicos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">LabPlot on rakendus teaduslike andmete interaktiivse graafikuna esitamiseks ja analüüsimiseks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">LabPlot datu zientifikoak modu elkarreragilean grafikatzeko eta aztertzeko aplikazio bat da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">LabPlot est une application pour le tracé interactif de courbes et l'analyse de données scientifiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">LabPlot é unha aplicación para a xeración interactiva de gráficos e a análise de datos científicos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">LabPlot adalah sebuah aplikasi untuk penggrafikan interaktif dan analisis data ilmiah.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">LabPlot è un'applicazione per i grafici interattivi e per l'analisi di dati scientifici.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">LabPlot2 is een toepassing voor het interactief maken van grafieken en het analyseren van wetenschappelijke gegevens.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">LabPlot er program for interaktiv plotting og analyse av vitskaplege data.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">LabPlot jest aplikacją do interaktywnego przestawiania graficznego i analizy danych naukowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O LabPlot é uma aplicação para gráficos interactivos e para a análise de dados científicos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O LabPlot é um aplicativo para criação de gráficos interativos e análise de dados científicos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">LabPlot — программа от KDE для анализа экспериментальных данных с возможностью интерактивного построения графиков.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">LabPlot je KDE aplikácia pre interaktívne grafy a analýzu vedeckých údajov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">LabPlot je aplikacija za interaktivno grafiko in analizo znanstvenih podatkov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Labplot är ett program för interaktiv diagramritning och analys av vetenskaplig data.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">LabPlot — програма для інтерактивної побудови графіків та аналізу наукових даних.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxLabPlot is an application for interactive graphing and analysis of scientific data.xx</p>
    <p>
      LabPlot provides an easy way to create, manage and edit plots. It allows you to produce plots based on data from a spreadsheet or on data imported from external files. Plots can be exported to several pixmap and vector graphic formats.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Grafikov LabPlot pruža jednostavan način za stvaranje, upravljanje i uređivanje crtanja dijagrama. On vam omogućava da proizvede crteže na osnovu podataka iz tabele ili podataka uvezenih iz eksternih fajlova. Crteži se mogu izvoziti u nekoliko pixmap i vektor grafičkih formata.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El LabPlot proporciona una manera fàcil de crear, gestionar i editar grafs. Permet produir grafs a partir de les dades d'un full de càlcul o en les dades importades des de fitxers externs. Els grafs es poden exportar a diversos formats de mapa de píxels i de gràfics vectorials.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El LabPlot proporciona una manera fàcil de crear, gestionar i editar grafs. Permet produir grafs a partir de les dades d'un full de càlcul o en les dades importades des de fitxers externs. Els grafs es poden exportar a diversos formats de mapa de píxels i de gràfics vectorials.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">LabPlot erlaubt es auf einfache Weise Grafiken zu erzeugen, zu verwalten und zu bearbeiten.Grafiken können aus externen Daten oder aus einer Tabelle erzeugt werden.Der Export der Grafiken in verschiedene Pixmap- und Vektorformate ist möglich.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το LabPlot παρέχει έναν εύκολο τρόπο δημιουργίας, διαχείρισης και επεξεργασίας γραφικών παραστάσεων. Σας επιτρέπει να δημιουργείτε γραφικές παρασασεις με βάση δεδομένα από φύλλα εργασίας ή εισηγμένα από εξωτερικά αρχεία. Οι γραφικές παραστάσεις μπορούν να εξαχθούν σε διάφορους τύπους αποθήκευσης χρωματικής περίπλεξης ή διανυσματικών γραφικών.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">LabPlot provides an easy way to create, manage and edit plots. It allows you to produce plots based on data from a spreadsheet or on data imported from external files. Plots can be exported to several pixmap and vector graphic formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">LabPlot proporciona un sencillo modo de crear, gestionar y editar gráficos. Le permite generar gráficos basados en datos obtenidos de una hoja de cálculo o importados de archivos externos. Los gráficos se pueden exportar a diversos formatos de imagen y vectoriales.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">LabPlot võimaldab vähese vaevaga jooniseid luua, hallata ja muuta. Graafikuid saab koostada andmetabelist pärit või võrgufailidest imporditud andmete põhjal. Jooniseid saab eksportida mitmes pikselraster- ja vektorgraafika vormingus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">LabPlot-ek grafikoak sortu, kudeatu eta editatzeko era erraz bat eskaintzen du. Grafikoak sortzen uzten dizu kalkulu-orrietako datuekin edo kanpoko fitxategietatik inportatutako datuekin. Grafikoak hainbat pixel-mapa eta bektore grafiko formatutara esportatu daitezke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">LabPlot tarjoaa helpon tavan luoda, hallita ja muokata kaavioita. Voit tuottaa kaavioita laskentataulukon tai muiden ulkoisten tiedostojen datasta. Kaavioita voi viedä eri bittikartta- ja vektorigrafiikkamuotoihin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">LabPlot fournit une moyen facile de créer, gérer et éditer des courbes. Il vous permet de produire des courbes produites à partir de données issues d'un tableur ou d'un fichier externe. Les courbes peuvent être exportées vers plusieurs format d'image matriciels ou vectoriels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">LabPlot fornece unha forma doada de crear, xestionar e editar gráficos. Permítelle producir gráficos baseados en datos dunha folla de cálculo ou datos importados de ficheiros externos. Pode exportar os gráficos en distintos formatos de imaxe, de mapas de píxeles ou vectoriais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">LabPlot menyediakan cara mudah untuk menciptakan, mengelola, dan mengedit plot. Ini memungkinkanmu menghasilkan plot berdasarkan data dari lembar-kerja atau data yang diimpor dari file eksternal. Plot bisa diekspor ke beberapa format grafik pixmap dan vector.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">LabPlot fornisce una modalità semplice per creare, gestire e modificare i grafici. Ti permette di generare grafici basati sui dati di un foglio elettronico, oppure importati da file esterni. I grafici possono essere esportati in diverse immagini e in diversi formati grafici vettoriali.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met LabPlot is het eenvoudig plots te maken, te beheren en te bewerken. U kunt er plots mee maken op basis van gegevens in een werkblad (spreadsheet), of van gegevens die uit externe bestanden zijn geïmporteerd. Plots kunnen worden geëxporteerd in diverse pixmap- of vector-grafische bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">LabPlot gjer det lett å laga, administrera og redigera plott. Du kan laga plott frå rekneark­data og data importert frå eksterne filer, og du kan eksportera plotta til fleire punkt- og vektorgrafikkformat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">LabPlot zapewnia łatwy sposób do tworzenia, zarządzania i edytowania wykresów. Umożliwia tworzenie wykresów na podstawie danych z arkusza kalkulacyjnego lub danych zaimportowanych z plików zewnętrznych. Wykresy można eksportować do kilku formatów graficznych map pikselowych i wektorowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O LabPlot oferece uma forma simples de criar, gerir e editar os gráficos. Permite-lhe produzir gráficos com base nos dados de uma folha de cálculo ou nos dados importados de ficheiros externos. Os gráficos podem ser exportados para diferentes formatos de imagens rasterizados e vectoriais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O LabPlot oferece uma forma simples de criar, gerenciar e editar gráficos. Permite-lhe produzir gráficos com base nos dados de uma planilha ou nos dados importados de arquivos externos. Os gráficos podem ser exportados para diferentes formatos de imagens rasterizadas e vetoriais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">LabPlot предоставляет простой способ создания, управления и редактирования графиков. Приложение позволяет создавать графики на основе данных из электронной таблицы или данных, импортированных из внешних файлов. Графики могут быть экспортированы в различные растровые и векторные графические форматы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">LabPlot poskytuje jednoduché možnosti na vytváranie, správu a úpravu nákresov. Umožní vám vyrobiť nákresy založené na údajoch z tabuľky alebo z údajov importovaných z externých súborov. Nákresy sa dajú exportovať do niekoľkých rastrových a vektorových grafických formátov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">LabPlot omogoča preprost način za ustvarjanje, upravljanje in urejanje grafikonov. Omogoča vam izdelavo slik na podlagi podatkov iz preglednice ali podatkov, uvoženih iz zunanje datoteke. Grafikone lahko izvozite v slike več različnih rastrskih in vektorskih formatov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Labplot tillhandahåller ett enkelt sätt att skapa, hantera och redigera diagram. Det låter dig skapa diagram baserat på data från ett kalkylark eller data importerad från externa filer. Diagram kan exporteras till flera olika punktavbildnings- och vektorgrafik-format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">LabPlot çizimleri oluşturmak, yönetmek ve düzenlemek için kolay bir yol sağlar. Bir tablodaki verilere veya harici dosyalardan alınan verilere dayalı çizimler üretmenizi sağlar. Çizimler çeşitli piksmap ve vektör grafik formatlarına aktarılabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою LabPlot просто створювати креслення, керувати ними та редагувати креслення. За допомогою програми можна створювати креслення на основі електронної таблиці або даних, імпортованих із зовнішнього файла. Креслення можна експортувати у форматі растрового або векторного зображення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxLabPlot provides an easy way to create, manage and edit plots. It allows you to produce plots based on data from a spreadsheet or on data imported from external files. Plots can be exported to several pixmap and vector graphic formats.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">LabPlot 提供了一种方便地创建、 管理和编辑图表的方式。它允许您基于电子表格的数据或从外部文件导入的数据来绘制图表。图表可以导出到多种格式的位图或矢量图形。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://labplot.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=LabPlot2&amp;format=guided</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Fit example</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Exemple d'ajust</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Exemple d'ajust</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Beispiel für Anpassung</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Fit example</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ejemplo de ajuste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Sobivuse näide</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Egokitzeko adibidea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Exemple d'ajustement</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Exemplo de axuste.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Contoh pas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Adatta esempio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Voorbeeld aanpassing</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Eksempel på kurvetilpassing</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Przykład dopasowania</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Exemplo de ajuste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Exemplo de ajuste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Пример автоподбора масштаба</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Primer prilagajanja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsexempel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Приклад апроксимації</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxFit examplexx</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/labplot2/labplot2_appdata_01.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Mathematical function</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Funció matemàtica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Funció matemàtica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Matematická funkce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Mathematische Funktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Mathematical function</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Función matemática</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Matemaatikafunktsioon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Funtzio matematikoa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Fonction mathématique</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Función matemática.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Fungsi matematika</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Funzione matematica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Wiskundige functie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Matematisk funksjon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Funkcja matematyczna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Função matemática</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Função matemática</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">График функции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Matematická funkcia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Matematična funkcija</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Matematisk funktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Математична функція</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMathematical functionxx</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/labplot2/labplot2_appdata_02.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>CAS worksheet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Full de treball CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Full de treball CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">CAS-Arbeitsblatt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">CAS worksheet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Hoja de trabajo CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">CAS tööleht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">CAS lan-orria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Feuille de travail CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Folla de traballo de CAS.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Lembar kerja CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Foglio di lavoro CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">CAS werkblad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">CAS-arbeidsark</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Arkusz roboczy CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Folha de cálculo CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Folha de trabalho CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Лист исходных данных</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Delovni list CAS</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">CAS-arbetsblad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Робочий аркуш СКА</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxCAS worksheetxx</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/labplot2/labplot2_appdata_03.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>labplot2</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.8.2" date="2021-04-01"/>
    <release version="2.8.1" date="2020-11-13"/>
    <release version="2.8.0" date="2020-09-16"/>
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::windows_store">https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9ngxfc68925l</value>
  </custom>
</component>
